I'm Brett Contras, the creator of 2x4
maximum strength. So, some of you will
be coming on to this website and you
don't know much about me. Now, I wear a
lot of hats. Here I am in my lab where I
conduct EMG and force plate and motion
capture research. Um, I'm also an
author. Um, I'm a writer. I I have a
popular
blog. I'm a personal trainer, strength
coach, but most importantly, I'm a
lifter just like you. And I'm always
looking for the answer. I'm always
trying to improve my own training so I
can achieve my best physique and achieve
my maximum strength. And when I designed
2x4, I put in a ton of effort. you know,
I'm not just some internet expert or
internet, you know, phony guy who, you
know, put just slapped together some
program. I actually put a ton of effort
forth. I reviewed all the past programs
that are successful, you know, examining
what they had in common and what was
different about them. I created my own
pro program and I trial trial it with
very strong power lifters. um you know,
not just beginner lifters who had a ton
to gain. I tried it on very experienced
lifters and even they gained a ton of
strength. So, I'm very very proud of my
system. I really think you'll love it
and I'm offering a 60-day money back
guarantee. So, if you don't like it, you
get your money back. So, really there's
no risk in trying it. Anyway, once
again, Brett Conurus, creator of 2x4. I
really think you'll love the resource.
It's not just a training program. I also
have some really cool bonus materials in
there uh on the on the biomechanics of
the squat and the deadlift on uh some
glute training findings that I've
recently discovered. So, give it a try.
I think you'll love it. Right now, I'm
going to show you clips of training and
competing. So, this is me a couple
months out uh doing conventional
deadlifts. That was
555 and I barely got that. That was
really hard for me. Then I switched to
sumo stance. This is the most I got in
training. This is
585. I don't think that would have
passed in a meet cuz I kind of hitched
at the top. But then here's me getting
601 at the
competition. Uh which I got it much
easier than I got the 585. I had a
really good tapering process. Um, but
anyway, my my deadlift went up, you
know, 15 pounds more than I've ever
done, but just in the last several
months, it went up, you know, like 50 lb
just in the last 5 months or so. Here's
bench press. Before I started doing 2x4,
I think I was doing 285 was my max. And
here's me getting 275 for five. And then
here's
305 with a
pause. And then the next clip shows
3:15, but I didn't pause here. So, I
just kind of bounce it up. So, that's
the most I did in
training. And then at the meet, I didn't
think I was going to get that much at
the meat cuz I you have to pause. But,
as you can see, at the meet, I ended up
doing three. This is 3:14.
They were calling really fast command,
so I ended up getting it a boy. But, uh,
yeah, my bench went up like, you know,
30 lbs. Here's me doing squats. This is
365 for three
reps. Uh, which when I start, before I
started 2x4, this was around my one rep
max. Yeah, 365 was my max. And now I'm
getting it three times. Here's me
getting
405. Up. Up. drive it. And then uh in
the meet I end up getting I believe 409
um that's
around a I
think 20 you know like a 30 lb gain in
my squat. Here's what's crazy. This is
six plates on each save. This is 585 and
I'm getting it for eight reps in the hip
thrust. My hip thrust strength. I really
hammered hip thrust the last 3 weeks
prior to my meet and about six twice a
week I would just hammer them. Here's
leg press. Now you uh I I remember doing
nine plates before and I could get like
one rep or two reps and here I am
getting
uh I
think six reps maybe. But anyways, much
easier. Here I got way stronger at all
my
lifts. Everything went up. Here's me
doing 45°ree back extensions. This is a
100 lb dumbbell and I have four 11lb
chains around my neck. This is 144
lbs.
Um, and I think I did like six. Now
moving on to Sammy. Here's Sammy
deadlifting 275.
Now that's her in the meat. I think she
got 293 or something like that. And then
this is after her meet. She got she kept
gaining strength. This is 225. And here,
look how fast that's flying up. That's
like speed deadlifts. Looks like nothing
to her. And one day I tested her one rep
max and she actually got 315. It's
coming up. So this is she's just flying
up with 225 against nothing here. Um, so
yeah, she ended up getting a 315. See,
there she is. She got 315. It's not the
prettiest form you've ever seen, but she
got it. So, there's Sammy achieving the
315 lb
deadlift. Um, here's Sammy squatting in
train in competition. I think her max
was like
210, but here she is getting 225. Here
she is getting 225 again.
And then here's one final clip of her
getting 225.
So, three different attempts, she ended
up getting 225 squat. And then here's a
105 bench press. So, she got gained a
ton of strength on on this program. This
is a 335 lb hip thrust for five
reps. Uh so, yeah, Sammy's strength was
incredible. She weighs like 125 lbs. So,
she ended up with a 315 deadlift, 225
squat, 105 bench. Um, here's another
clip of her hip thrusting. This is
365. So, she gets three reps for
365. She's got some very strong glutes,
which I think helps her deadlift a
lot. Now, moving on. This is Aaron. Uh
Aaron ended up squatting
um I believe
140ish and deadlifting 210. There she is
deadlifting. Now she can deadlift 225.
And this is Rob, my buddy Rob from last
year who competed with me at the first
powerlifting competition. So his squat
and deadlift both went up like 50 lbs.
He put 50 lbs on his squat and
deadlift. Here's Andrew with a front
squat. Crazy front squat strength.
Here's him doing block pulls. Uh this is
515. The he gained Andrew gained the
most strength out of anyone on
2x4 floor pressing
345. Andrew's hip thrust went way up. He
was doing like 365 and 405 and then he
moved up to doing
495. Here's
a 525
squat and
a a
560 deadlift. And then in here's him
competing. He ended up with a
525 squat in in competition, a 365 bench
press, nice and a
565 deadlift, I believe.